<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.4.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-02-07T00:12:36+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000//</id><title type="html">Niroz Jung Karki</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to my first Blogpost</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/05/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to my first Blogpost" /><published>2017-02-05T18:07:12+01:00</published><updated>2017-02-05T18:07:12+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/05/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/05/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;This is my first blogpost. I actually had a portfolio hosted in 1 und 1 server but later decided to go for opensource and make most of it. After coming across jekyll, I had a strong feeling of giving up my portfolio website hosted in commerical 1und1 servers for which I already terminated with end of this year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Life is so interesting, and so technologies changing everyday. Keeping your blogposts uptodate and writing somthing real and updating is kind of cumbersome work but howevery with the advent of 2017 I am determined to create some values within myself and try write creative stuffs from personal career growth to software technolgies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, there are lots of things to learn in life and I am continuosly struggling to find time admidst these distractions. I have several ways how i keep myself controlled in distractive social medias where you get everything what you want every momentary gratifications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing contantly triggers my mind, what and how can I add value to my society using technology and internet. I would be very much glad if people sharing common interests to shout at me and I will shout you back and wish to have a wonderful colloborative teamwork to create value withing us, may it be in social entrerenurial or anything commerical to agriculture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://nirozjungkarki.com&quot;&gt;nirozjungkarki.com&lt;/a&gt; for more info about me. All my works will be hosted in my &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/nirozjung&quot;&gt;GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have want to donate for my work, you can are mostly welcome at &lt;a href=&quot;https://paypal.me/jungkarki&quot;&gt;Paypal Donate&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">This is my first blogpost. I actually had a portfolio hosted in 1 und 1 server but later decided to go for opensource and make most of it. After coming across jekyll, I had a strong feeling of giving up my portfolio website hosted in commerical 1und1 servers for which I already terminated with end of this year.</summary></entry></feed>
